const BBDL_FULL_QUIZZES = [
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q01",
        question: "Which Licence Condition clauses cover the rules on using Regional Secondary Locators (RSL)?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Licence 4-1a and 4-1b",
            "Licence 5-1 and 6-7",
            "Licence 6-22, 6-23 and 6-24",
            "Licence 8-1a, 8-1b, 8-2 and 8-3",
        ],
        correct: 2,
        explanation: "RSL is also mentioned in 6-25.",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q02",
        question: "Where in the Licence would you look to find out how often you must transmit your callsign?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Licence 6-19b",
            "Licence 6-21b",
            "Licence 7-1a",
            "Licence 9-3a",
        ],
        correct: 1,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q03",
        question: "Where does your Licence say that your Radio Equipment can be operated by anyone that has your permission and is under your direct supervision?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Licence 1-1",
            "Licence 2-2",
            "Licence 6-6",
            "Licence 6-8",
        ],
        correct: 2,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q04",
        question: "Licence 7-1 says that you must permit any person authorised by Ofcom to inspect your Licence and Radio Equipment. What does the word 'inspect' include?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Visual observation and test",
            "Visual observation only",
            "Examine and test",
            "Examine only",
        ],
        correct: 2,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q05",
        question: "When recording a Message from another amateur and retransmitting it, the Licensee must:",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "include all callsigns",
            "remove all callsigns",
            "only transmit their own callsign",
            "ensure that their transmission is identifiable at all times",
        ],
        correct: 3,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q06",
        question: "Under normal circumstances, which of the following must NOT be sent from an amateur radio station?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "coded messages",
            "encrypted messages",
            "details of technical investigations",
            "any transmissions that do not elicit a reply",
        ],
        correct: 1,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q07",
        question: "The Licence sets up some rules about transmissions being stable and free from unwanted emissions. Where would you find these rules?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Licence 1-2",
            "Licence 2-2",
            "Licence 6-2",
            "Licence 8-2",
        ],
        correct: 2,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q08",
        question: "There is a very specific rule on the frequencies that should be used for remote control link. Where in the Licence are the frequencies specified?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "The Notice of Coordination",
            "The Schedule, Table C",
            "Licence 9-6",
            "Licence 6-10b",
        ],
        correct: 3,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q09",
        question: "CEPT Recommendation T/R 61-01 governs the use of amateur radio in other countries. Where is that recommendation defined?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Page 2 of the Licence",
            "Notes to Schedule 1",
            "Licence 6-10b",
            "Licence 10-1d",
        ],
        correct: 3,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q10",
        question: "The UK Licence allows any Licensee to operate at sea, but only on a ship that is registered in the UK, the Channel Islands or the Isle of Man. Which of the following include important information appertaining to such use?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Licence 4-1b",
            "Licence 10-1b",
            "Note s to Schedule 1",
            "Page 2 of the Licence",
        ],
        correct: 0,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q11",
        question: "When a Full Licence holder is operating a Beacon which has its own callsign, which of the following dictates the maximum transmitter power?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "the information on Page 1 of the Licence",
            "the band plan for the frequency in use",
            "Schedule 1 Table B",
            "Licence 6-13",
        ],
        correct: 3,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q12",
        question: "Which of the following bands has an amateur satellite allocation?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "1240-1260MHz",
            "2310-2350MHz",
            "5650-5670MHz",
            "5820-5830MHz",
        ],
        correct: 2,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q13",
        question: "The frequency band 7.000-7.100MHz is:",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Primary",
            "Secondary",
            "Shared",
            "Avaliable on the basis of non-interference to other services",
        ],
        correct: 0,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q14",
        question: "Where in the Licence will you find specific rules about operating on the 5MHz band?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Licence 6-20",
            "Licence 9-7",
            "Note G to Schedule 1",
            "Note G to the Notice of Coordination",
        ],
        correct: 2,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q15",
        question: "The UK rules on exposure to EMF from amateur radio are:",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "in the relevant tables for general public exposure identified in the ICNIRP Guidelines",
            "only applicable to transmitters with power levels above 10 Watts",
            "set out in Condition 9 of the Licence",
            "regulated by the RSGB on behalf of Ofcom",
        ],
        correct: 2,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q16",
        question: "The purpose of the EMF restrictions set out in the UK amateur radio licence is to prevent:",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "other users of wireless telegraphy suffering potentially harmful interference",
            "radio workers being exposed to potentially harmful levels of ionising electromagnetic radiation",
            "radio amateurs exposong themselves to potentially harmful levels of non-ionising ekectromagnetic radiation",
            "the general public being exposed to levels of non-ionising electromagnetic radiation above the basic restrictions set out in tables",
        ],
        correct: 3,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q17",
        question: "The Licence says that you may only use 'Relevant Radio Equipment' if the total EMF exposure levels do not exceed the ICNIRP Guidelines. What is the definition of 'Relevant Radio Equipment'?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "any Radio Equipmennt owned by the Licence Holder",
            "any transmitting apparatus on the site, regardless of ownership and radiated power",
            "Radio Equipment authorised by the Licence that transmits at powers greater than 10W EIRP or 6.1W ERP",
            "any transmitting apparatus owned by the Licence Holder that is capable of transmitting at powers greater than 10W EIRP or 6.1W ERP",
        ],
        correct: 2,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q18",
        question: "Around which frequency would you expect to find other UK stations using Low Power Morse Code?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "5060kHz",
            "5262kHz",
            "Anywhere between 5284.0kHz and 5288.5kHz",
            "Anywhere between 5351.5kHz and 5366.5kHz",
        ],
        correct: 1,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q19",
        question: "Which mode is NOT recommended (and would also be illegal) for use in the 472kHz (600m) band?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "Narrow Band Frequency Modulation",
            "Narrow Band digital modes",
            "QRSS",
            "CW",
        ],
        correct: 0,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
    {
        source: "BBDL QUIZ WEEK00 Q20",
        question: "Where would you find the formula to work out the combined value of any number of similar components connected in parallel?",
        image: "",
        options: [
            "in Schedule 1 of the Licence",
            "in Schedule 2 of the Licence",
            "in Column 1 of the Formula Sheet in EX309",
            "in Column 2 of the Formula Sheet in EX309",
        ],
        correct: 3,
        explanation: "",
        lookup: "See page(s) x of the Full Licence text book",
        syllabus: "0"
    },
]

export default BBDL_FULL_QUIZZES